[
{"question": "Who was the first President of Pakistan?", "options": ["Liaquat Ali Khan", "Iskander Mirza", "Ayub Khan", "Zulfiqar Ali Bhutto"], "correctAnswer": "Iskander Mirza", "submittedBy": "Dummy User", "detailsUrl": "#"},
{"question": "Which year did the Objective Resolution pass?", "options": ["1947", "1948", "1949", "1950"], "correctAnswer": "1949", "submittedBy": "Dummy User", "detailsUrl": "#"},
{"question": "Who was the first Chief Justice of Pakistan?", "options": ["Abdul Rashid", "Cornelius", "Munir", "Shahabuddin"], "correctAnswer": "Abdul Rashid", "submittedBy": "Dummy User", "detailsUrl": "#"},
{"question": "Which amendment made Pakistan an Islamic Republic?", "options": ["1st", "2nd", "3rd", "None"], "correctAnswer": "None", "submittedBy": "Dummy User", "detailsUrl": "#"},
{"question": "Who was the founder of All India Muslim League?", "options": ["Sir Syed Ahmed Khan", "Nawab Salimullah Khan", "Aga Khan III", "Liaquat Ali Khan"], "correctAnswer": "Nawab Salimullah Khan", "submittedBy": "Dummy User", "detailsUrl": "#"},
{"question": "Which city is called the 'City of Saints'?", "options": ["Lahore", "Multan", "Karachi", "Peshawar"], "correctAnswer": "Multan", "submittedBy": "Dummy User", "detailsUrl": "#"},
{"question": "Who was the first female Prime Minister of Pakistan?", "options": ["Fatima Jinnah", "Benazir Bhutto", "Hina Rabbani Khar", "Asma Jahangir"], "correctAnswer": "Benazir Bhutto", "submittedBy": "Dummy User", "detailsUrl": "#"},
{"question": "Which is the largest province of Pakistan by area?", "options": ["Punjab", "Sindh", "Balochistan", "KPK"], "correctAnswer": "Balochistan", "submittedBy": "Dummy User", "detailsUrl": "#"},
{"question": "Who was the first Governor General of Pakistan?", "options": ["Liaquat Ali Khan", "Quaid-e-Azam", "Ayub Khan", "Iskander Mirza"], "correctAnswer": "Quaid-e-Azam", "submittedBy": "Dummy User", "detailsUrl": "#"},
{"question": "Which river is called the lifeline of Pakistan?", "options": ["Indus", "Jhelum", "Chenab", "Ravi"], "correctAnswer": "Indus", "submittedBy": "Dummy User", "detailsUrl": "#"}
] 